{
    "subject": "Alan_Rudolph",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Trixie__film_",
    "human_readable": "Alan Rudolph directed the film Trixie.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9619803428649902,
            "question": "Name a film Alan Rudolph has directed."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9004454016685486,
            "question": "Who directed the film Trixie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8688854575157166,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Alan Rudolph?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7264425754547119,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Alan Rudolph?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.674365758895874,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a film directed by Alan Rudolph?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6378336548805237,
            "question": "What actors were in the film Trixie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5549720525741577,
            "question": "What year was the film Trixie released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4177720248699188,
            "question": "Where can I watch the film Trixie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40965256094932556,
            "question": "What genre is the film Trixie likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3396260738372803,
            "question": "Is there a trailer for the film Trixie available online?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alan Rudolph directed the film Trixie.",
            "html": "yago_9749_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Trixie likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_9749_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch the film Trixie?",
            "html": "yago_9749_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Trixie released?",
            "html": "yago_9749_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9749_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9749_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9749_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9749_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9749_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9749_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9749_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9749_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9749_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9749_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Alan Rudolph directed the film Trixie.\" Several pieces of evidence include:\n\n- Document `9.txt`: Mentions \"Trixie,\" Alan Rudolph\u2019s new comedy-mystery.\n- Document `27.txt`: States \"Trixie is a 2000 American mystery-crime film directed by Alan Rudolph.\"\n- Document `105.txt`: Also confirms that Trixie was directed by Alan Rudolph and provides additional details about the cast."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}